BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 17) 6178/017
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Stone Cutters - Milwaukee, WI, 1915 (Box 14, Folder 115)
- Stone Cutters - Joliet, IL, 1925-1927 (Box 14, Folder 116)
- Stone Cutters - Bloomington, IL, 1923 (Box 14, Folder 117)
- Stone Cutters - Evansville, IN, 1904-1919 (Box 14, Folder 118)
  1904, 1919
- Stone Cutters - Indianapolis, IN, 1906-1920 (Box 14, Folder 119)
  1906, 1918, 1919, 1920
- Stone Cutters - Tacoma, WA, 1923 (Box 14, Folder 120)
- Stone Cutters - Elgin, IL, 1901 (Box 14, Folder 121)
- Stone Cutters - National, 1913-1914 (Box 14, Folder 122)
- Stone Cutters - Birmingham, AL, 1890-1902 (Box 14, Folder 123)
  1890, 1902
- Stone Cutters - San Francisco, CA, 1907-1912 (Box 14, Folder 124)
  1907, 1912
- Stone Cutters - New Haven, CT, 1914 (Box 14, Folder 125)
- Stone Cutters - Washington D.C., 1915-1923 (Box 14, Folder 126)
- Stone Cutters - Atlanta, GA, 1905-1921 (Box 14, Folder 127)
- Stone Cutters - Champaign, IL, 1923 (Box 14, Folder 128)
- Stone Cutters - National (Box 14, Folder 129)
- Stone Cutters - New York, NY, 1913 (Box 14, Folder 130)
- Stone Cutters - Rochester, NY, 1919-1928 (Box 14, Folder 131)
- Stone Cutters - Niagara Falls, NY, 1926 (Box 14, Folder 132)
- Stone Cutters - Manhattan, KS, 1906 (Box 14, Folder 133)
- Stone Cutters - Boston, MA, 1914-1926 (Box 14, Folder 134)
  1914, 1915, 1926
- Stone Cutters - Wichita, KS, 1917-1918 (Box 14, Folder 135)
  1917, 1918
- Stone Cutters - Bowling Green, KY, 1926 (Box 14, Folder 136)
- Stone Cutters - Lexington, KY, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 137)
- Stone Cutters - Baltimore, Mary., 1915-1924 (Box 14, Folder 138)
- Stone Cutters - Detroit, MI, 1902-1916 (Box 14, Folder 139)
  1902, 1914, 1916
- Stone Cutters - Lincoln, NE, 1923 (Box 14, Folder 140)
- Stone Cutters - Kasota, MN, 1899 (Box 14, Folder 141)
- Stone Cutters - St. Paul, MN, 1899-1925 (Box 14, Folder 142)
  1899, 1925
- Stone Cutters - Kansas City, MO, 1914-1923 (Box 14, Folder 143)
- Stone Cutters - St. Louis, MO, 1907-1916 (Box 14, Folder 144)
  1907, 1916
- Stone Cutters - Muncie, IN, 1905 (Box 14, Folder 145)
- Stone Cutters - Newark, NJ, 1917 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Stone Cutters - Cedar Rapids, IA, 1926 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Stone Cutters - Buffalo, NY, 1910-1917 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  1910, 1917
- Stone Cutters - New York, NY, 1904-1916 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  1904, 1913, 1916
- Stone Masons - Philadelphia, PA, 1912 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Stone Planermen - Chicago, IL, 1916 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Stores - Roslyn, WA, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Street and Public Utility Inspectors - Chicago, IL, 1926 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Teamsters - Detroit, MI, 1914 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Teamsters - Tacoma, WA, 1916-1925 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  1916, 1920, 1923, 1925
- Teamsters - Spokane, WA, 1920-1924 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  1920, 1921, 1922, 1923, 1924
- Teamsters - Butte, MT, 1913-1923 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  1913, 1916, 1918, 1920, 1922, 1923
- Teamsters - St. Louis, MO, 1918-1924 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Teamsters - Jersey City, NJ, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Teamsters - Manchester, NH, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Teamsters - Omaha, NE, 1917-1918 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Teamsters - New York, NY, 1914-1920 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Teamsters - Buffalo, NY, 1919 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Teamsters - Jersey City, NJ, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Teamsters - San Francisco, CA, 1922-1926 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Teamsters - St. Louis, MO, 1913-1922 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Teamsters - Seattle, WA, 1916-1925 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Teamsters - Salt Lake City, UT, 1918 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Teamsters (Taxi) - Seattle, WA, 1924-1926 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Teamsters - National, 1916 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Teamsters - Wheeling, PA, 1919-1920 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Teamsters - Milwaukee, WI, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Teamsters - Cheyenne, WY, 1922-1923 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Teamsters - Providence, RI, 1915-1922 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  1915- 1922
- Teamsters - Scranton, PA, 1914 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Teamsters (Bakers, Driers and Salesmen) - Indianapolis, IN, 1914-1918 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  1914, 1915, 1917, 1918
- Teamsters (Bakery Wagon Drivers) - Detroit, MI, 1917 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Teamsters (Bakery Wagon Drivers) - South Chicago, IL, 1917 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Teamsters - Pittsburgh, PA, 1917 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Teamsters - Scranton, PA, 1927 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Teamsters - Belleville, IL, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Teamsters - Bloomington, IL, 1919 (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Teamsters - National, 1913 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Teamsters - New Orleans, LA, 1910-1915 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  1910, 1913, 1915
- Teamsters (Chauffeurs) - Kansas City, MO, 1913-1915 (Box 15, Folder 40)
- Teamsters - Chicago, IL, 1922-1927 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  1922, 1925, 1927
- Teamsters - Bakersfield, CA, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 42)
- Teamsters - Los Angeles, CA, 1915-1920 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  1915, 1916, 1920
- Teamsters - Kansas City, MO, 1919 (Box 15, Folder 44)
- Teamsters (Coal) - Portland, ME, 1918-1920 (Box 15, Folder 45)
- Teamsters (Coal) - Boston, MA, 1923-1926 (Box 15, Folder 46)
- Teamsters - Lynn, MA, 1916-1926 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  1916, 1918, 1920, 1926
- Teamsters - Watertown, MA, 1923-1924 (Box 15, Folder 48)
- Teamsters - Philadelphia, PA, 1918 (Box 15, Folder 49)
- Teamsters (Team Drivers) - Portland, OR, 1917-1920 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  1917, 1918, 1920
- Teamsters - Oakland, CA, 1923 (Box 15, Folder 51)
- Teamsters - Topeka, KS, 1919 (Box 15, Folder 52)
- Teamsters - Pittsburg, KS, 1923 (Box 15, Folder 53)
- Teamsters - Wichita, KS, 1918 (Box 15, Folder 54)
- Teamsters - Cleveland, OH, 1912-1915 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  1912, 1915
- Teamsters (Truck Drivers) - Detroit, MI, 1914-1917 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  1914, 1915, 1916, 1917
- Teamsters - San Francisco, CA, 1912-1923 (Box 15, Folder 57)
- Teamsters - Chicago, IL, 1914-1920 (Box 15, Folder 58)
  1914, 1915, 1917, 1920
- Teamsters - Peoria, IL, 1918-1924 (Box 15, Folder 59)
  1918, 1919, 1920, 1922, 1924
- Teamsters - Quincy, IL, 1923 (Box 15, Folder 60)
- Teamsters - Davenport, IA, 1917-1920 (Box 15, Folder 61)
- Teamsters - Des Moines, IA, 1912-1925 (Box 15, Folder 62)
  1912, 1923, 1924, 1925
- Teamsters - La Salle, IL, 1916 (Box 15, Folder 63)
- Teamsters - East St. Louis, MO, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 64)
- Teamsters - South Chicago, IL, 1923-1927 (Box 15, Folder 65)
- Teamsters (Auto Livery Chauffeurs) - Chicago, IL, 1913-1924 (Box 15, Folder 66)
  1913, 1916, 1919-1924
- Carbonated Water Wagon Drivers - Memphis, TN, 1913-1915 (Box 15, Folder 67)
  1913, 1914, 1915
- Teamsters (Carriage Drivers) - Cincinnati, OH, 1913-1923 (Box 15, Folder 68)
- Teamsters (Chauffeurs) - Rochester, NY, 1918-1923 (Box 15, Folder 69)
- Teamsters (Chauffeurs) - Cleveland, OH, 1915 (Box 15, Folder 70)
- Teamsters (Chauffeurs) - Houston, TX, 1923 (Box 15, Folder 71)
- Teamsters (Drivers) - New York, NY, 1914-1926 (Box 15, Folder 72)
  1914-1921, 1926
- Teamsters (Clothing Drivers) - New York, NY, 1914-1919 (Box 15, Folder 73)
  1914, 1918, 1919
- Teamsters (Coal) - Worcester, MA, 1915-1916 (Box 15, Folder 74)
- Teamsters (Coal) - New York, NY, 1914-1926 (Box 15, Folder 75)
  1914, 1917-1922, 1925, 1926
- Teamsters (Coal) - Providence, RI, 1916 (Box 15, Folder 76)
- Teamsters (Coal) - St. Louis, MO, 1914-1921 (Box 15, Folder 77)
  1914, 1916, 1918, 1920, 1921
- Coal Drivers - Cincinnati, OH, 1920-1923 (Box 15, Folder 78)
- Coffee and Tea Drivers - Seattle, WA, 1917 (Box 15, Folder 79)
- Commission Wagon Drivers - Seattle, WA, 1916-1918 (Box 15, Folder 80)
- Commission Drivers - Cincinnati, OH, 1917 (Box 15, Folder 81)
- Commission Drivers - Newark, NJ, 1913-1916 (Box 15, Folder 82)
  1913, 1914, 1916
- Commission Drivers and Helpers - New York, NY, 1912-1927 (Box 15, Folder 83)
  1912, 1916, 1917, 1919, 1920, 1927
- Teamsters (Dairy Division) - Cleveland, OH, 1918 (Box 15, Folder 84)
- Teamsters (Dairy Division) - Seattle, WA, 1919 (Box 15, Folder 85)
- Teamsters (Dairy Division) - Cincinnati, OH, 1914-1923 (Box 15, Folder 86)
  1914, 1916, 1919, 1921, 1923
- Teamsters (Department Store Drivers) - St. Louis, MO, 1912-1916 (Box 15, Folder 87)
  1912, 1915, 1916
- Dump Trucks and Subway - New York, NY, 1926 (Box 15, Folder 88)
- Teamsters (Baggagemen) - St. Louis, MO, 1913 (Box 15, Folder 89)
- Bakery Salesmen - Kansas City, MO, 1915-1923 (Box 15, Folder 90)
- Bakery Wagon Drivers and Salesmen - Oakland, CA, 1919 (Box 15, Folder 91)
- Bakery Wagon Drivers and Salesmen - Washington D.C., 1912-1926 (Box 15, Folder 92)
- Bakery Wagon Drivers and Salesmen - San Francisco, CA, 1917-1923 (Box 15, Folder 93)
  1917, 1918, 1919, 1923
- Bakery Wagon Drivers - Chicago, IL, 1914-1926 (Box 15, Folder 94)
  1914-1917, 1920-1926
- Bakery Drivers and Salesmen - Scranton, PA, 1916 (Box 15, Folder 95)
- Bakery Wagon Drivers - Cincinnati, OH, 1915-1927 (Box 15, Folder 96)
  1915, 1919, 1921, 1925, 1927
- Bakery Wagon Drivers - St. Louis, MO, 1916 (Box 15, Folder 97)
- Beef and Provision Drivers - Newark, NJ, 1916-1923 (Box 15, Folder 98)
- Beer and Mineral Water Bottlers - Scranton, PA, 1915-1916 (Box 15, Folder 99)
- Beer Drivers - Milwaukee, WI, 1912-1915 (Box 15, Folder 100)
- Bone and Tallow Teamsters - Chicago, IL, 1912-1919 (Box 15, Folder 101)
  1912, 1916, 1917, 1918, 1919
- Bottlers and Drivers - Butte, MT, 1915 (Box 15, Folder 102)
- Beer Wagon Drivers - South Chicago, IL, 1914-1917 (Box 15, Folder 103)
- Brewery Workers - Rochester, NY, 1914 (Box 15, Folder 104)
- Brick, Sand, and Terra Cotta Teamsters - Chicago, IL, 1913-1917 (Box 15, Folder 105)
  1913, 1915, 1916, 1917
- Building Material Teamsters - New York, NY, 1916-1924 (Box 15, Folder 106)
  1916, 1918, 1920, 1923, 1924
- Building Material Teamsters - Chicago, IL, 1918-1920 (Box 15, Folder 107)
- Building Materials Team Drivers - San Francisco, CA, 1914-1923 (Box 15, Folder 108)
  1914, 1916, 1918, 1919, 1923
- Bus Operators - Bayonne, NJ, 1927 (Box 15, Folder 109)
- Building Material Drivers - Cincinnati, OH, 1915 (Box 15, Folder 110)
- Teamsters and Chauffeurs - Rochester, NY, 1915-1921 (Box 15, Folder 111)
  1915, 1916, 1920, 1921
- Sanitary Department Drivers - Wheeling, WV, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 112)
- Coal Teamsters - St. Louis, MO, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 113)
- Chauffeurs and Teamsters - St. Louis, MO, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 114)
- Teamsters and Chauffeurs - Toledo, OH, 1917-1919 (Box 15, Folder 115)
- Teamsters and Chauffeurs - Vallejo, CA, 1919 (Box 15, Folder 116)
- Teamsters and Chauffeurs - Bridgeport, CT, 1916 (Box 15, Folder 117)
- Commission Drivers - Chicago, IL, 1910-1916 (Box 15, Folder 118)
  1910, 1913, 1916
- Chauffeurs - Jacksonville, FL, 1916 (Box 15, Folder 119)
- Team Drivers and Chauffeurs - St. Paul, MN, 1913-1918 (Box 15, Folder 120)
  1913, 1917, 1918
- Teamsters and Chauffeurs - Cleveland, OH, 1921-1923 (Box 15, Folder 121)
- Teamsters and Chauffeurs - Detroit, MI, 1921 (Box 15, Folder 122)
- Carriage Drivers and Chauffeurs - Boston, MA, 1915-1918 (Box 15, Folder 123)
  1915, 1916, 1918
- Carriage and Livery Drivers - Chicago, IL, 1910 (Box 15, Folder 124)
- Dairy Employees - Chicago, IL, 1924-1927 (Box 15, Folder 125)
  1924, 1925, 1927
- Carriage and Cab Drivers - Chicago, IL, 1905-1906 (Box 15, Folder 126)
- Coal Teamsters - Chicago, IL, 1912-1925 (Box 15, Folder 127)
  1912, 1915, 1918-1925
- Drivers, Chauffeurs, Stablemen and Helpers - Portland, ME, 1920-1923 (Box 15, Folder 128)
- Department Store Drivers - Boston, MA, 1914 (Box 15, Folder 129)
- Department Store Drivers - South Chicago, IL, 1913 (Box 15, Folder 130)
- Carriage Drivers and Chauffeurs - Boston, MA, 1920-1925 (Box 15, Folder 131)
- Commission Drivers - Chicago, IL, 1917-1925 (Box 15, Folder 132)
  1917, 1918, 1919, 1920, 1922, 1925
- Coal Teamsters - Boston, MA, 1913-1922 (Box 15, Folder 133)
  1913, 1916-1922
- Coal Teamsters - Springfield, MA, 1918 (Box 15, Folder 134)
- Coal Teamsters - Worcester, MA, 1919 (Box 15, Folder 135)
- Chauffeurs - San Francisco, CA, 1915-1925 (Box 15, Folder 136)
  1915-1920, 1924, 1925
- Coal Teamsters - Philadelphia, PA, 1913-1919 (Box 15, Folder 137)
  1913, 1916, 1917, 1919
- Freight and Furniture Movers - Portland, OR, 1917 (Box 15, Folder 138)
- Commission House Teamsters - South Chicago, IL, 1913-1917 (Box 15, Folder 139)
- Drivers and Stablemen - Lowell, MA, 1923 (Box 15, Folder 140)
- Drivers and Chauffeurs - New York, NY, 1918-1925 (Box 15, Folder 141)
  1918, 1919, 1920, 1925
- Carriage Drivers - St. Louis, MO, 1915-1925 (Box 15, Folder 142)
  1915, 1916, 1918, 1920, 1924, 1925
- Excavating Teamsters - Boston, MA, 1914-1919 (Box 15, Folder 143)
- Excavating Teamsters - New York, NY, 1912-1917 (Box 15, Folder 144)
  1912, 1915, 1917
- Excavating Teamsters - Newark, NJ, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 145)
- Excavating Teamsters - Chicago, IL, 1913-1924 (Box 15, Folder 146)
  1913, 1915, 1918-1924
- Excavating Teamsters - Cleveland, OH, 1916-1924 (Box 15, Folder 147)
  1916-1918, 1921, 1924
- United Building Material Drivers - New York, NY, 1915 (Box 15, Folder 148)
- Express, Baggage, and Parcel Wagon Drivers - South Chicago, IL, 1915 (Box 15, Folder 149)
- Express Drivers - New York, NY, 1913-1925 (Box 15, Folder 150)
- Expressmen - Newark, NJ, 1915-1924 (Box 15, Folder 151)
  1915, 1920, 1924
- Flour Teamsters - New York, NY, 1917-1919 (Box 15, Folder 152)
  1917, 1918, 1919
- Fruit and Produce Drivers - Philadelphia, PA, 1914 (Box 15, Folder 153)
- Funeral Drivers - New York, NY, 1912-1920 (Box 15, Folder 154)
  1912, 1915, 1917, 1919, 1920
- Funeral Drivers - St. Louis, MO, 1925-1926 (Box 15, Folder 155)
- Furniture Drivers - New York, NY, 1914-1925 (Box 15, Folder 156)
  1914, 1915, 1925
- Furniture and Piano Movers - Boston, MA, 1913-1919 (Box 15, Folder 157)
- Furniture and Piano Movers - South Chicago, IL, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 158)
- Furniture and Department Store Drivers - Chicago, IL, 1912-1920 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  1912, 1916-1920
- Furniture Drivers - Chicago, IL, 1927 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Furniture and Department Store Drivers - Providence, RI, 1913-1921 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Furniture Movers and Drivers - New York, NY, 1913-1920 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  1913, 1914, 1917-1920
- Furniture Drivers - St. Louis, MO, 1913-1924 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  1913, 1916-1924
- Furniture and Piano Movers - Cincinnati, OH, 1917-1925 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  1917, 1919, 1922, 1924, 1925
- General Teamsters - Indianapolis, IN, 1913-1915 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- General Teamsters - South Chicago, IL, 1913-1923 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  1913, 1915, 1917, 1919, 1920, 1923
- General Teamsters - Minneapolis, MN, 1916-1917 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- General Teamsters - Worcester, MA, 1916 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- General Teamsters - Chicago, IL, 1913-1925 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- General Teamsters - Madison, WI, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- General Teamsters - Philadelphia, PA, 1913-1919 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- General Teamsters - Dayton, OH, 1919 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Grain and Mason Supply Teamsters - Springfield, MA, 1918 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Grease Teamsters - Chicago, IL, 1914-1919 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  1914, 1915, 1916, 1917, 1919
- Grocery and Market Teamsters - South Chicago, IL, 1913-1919 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  1913, 1917, 1919
- Grocery and Market Drivers - Chicago, IL, 1917 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Grocery Teamsters - New York, NY, 1917-1919 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Grocery Teamsters - Cleveland, OH, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Hock Driers - Worcester, MA, 1916 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Cab Drivers - Kansas City, MO, 1915 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Hay and Grain Teamsters - Chicago, IL, 1913-1926 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  1913, 1916, 1920, 1923, 1926
- Cab and Delivery Drivers - Houston, TX, 1915-1924 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Ice Wagon Drivers - Cincinnati, OH, 1914-1925 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Ice Wagon Drivers - St. Louis, MO, 1914-1926 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Ice Wagon Drivers - Cleveland, OH, 1919-1920 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Ice Wagon Drivers - Dallas, TX, 1915 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Ice Drivers - Cleveland, OH, 1915-1927 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Ice Wagon Drivers - Seattle, WA, 1926-1927 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Ice Cream Drivers - Cleveland, OH, 1920-1923 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Ice Cream Drivers - Cincinnati, OH, 1914-1923 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Ice Wagon Drivers - Rochester, NY, 1913-1926 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  1913, 1915, 1923, 1924, 1926
- Ice Wagon Drivers - Toledo, OH, 1920 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Ice Wagon Drivers - Chicago, IL, 1915-1923 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  1915, 1917, 1918, 1919, 1920, 1923
- Ice Wagon Drivers and Helpers - San Francisco, CA, 1914-1925 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  1914-1920, 1923, 1925
- Ice Wagon Drivers - Columbus, OH, 1915-1923 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  1915, 1918, 1919, 1920, 1922, 1923
- Ice Wagon Drivers - Chicago, IL, 1912-1921 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  1912, 1921
- Ice Handlers - Peoria, IL, 1916-1920 (Box 16, Folder 39)
- Ice Wagon Drivers - Minneapolis, MN, 1914-1922 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  1914, 1916, 1920, 1922
- Ice Cream Wagon Drivers - Washington D.C., 1916-1925 (Box 16, Folder 41)
- Ice Wagon Drivers - Detroit, MI, 1914-1920 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  1914, 1917, 1919, 1920
- Ice Wagon Drivers - Davenport, IA, 1917 (Box 16, Folder 43)
- Ice Wagon Drivers - Dayton, OH, 1920-1922 (Box 16, Folder 44)
- Keg Beer Wagon Drivers - Chicago, IL, 1914-1917 (Box 16, Folder 45)
- Keg Beer Drivers - Los Angeles, CA, 1913-1916 (Box 16, Folder 46)
- Laundry Drivers - Memphis, TN, 1917 (Box 16, Folder 47)
- Laundry and Dye Work Drivers - Seattle, WA, 1918-1919 (Box 16, Folder 48)
- Laundry Drivers - New York, NY, 1924 (Box 16, Folder 49)
- Laundry and Dye House Drivers - n/a, 1914-1918 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  1914, 1916, 1917, 1918
- Laundry and Dye House Drivers - Chicago, IL, 1916-1925 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  1916, 1917, 1918, 1919, 1925
- Laundry Teamsters - South Chicago, IL, 1913-1917 (Box 16, Folder 52)
- Livery Teamsters - South Chicago, IL, 1913-1915 (Box 16, Folder 53)
- Lumber Teamsters - Lawrence, MA, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 54)
- Laundry Wagon Drivers - Boston, MA, 1916-1919 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  1916, 1917, 1918, 1919
- Lumber Teamsters - Boston, MA, 1914-1919 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  1914, 1917, 1918, 1919
- Lumber Teamsters - Chicago, IL, 1912-1926 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  1912, 1915-1919, 1922-1926
- Lumber Teamsters - Philadelphia, PA, 1916-1920 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  1916, 1917, 1918, 1920
- Market and Commission House Teamsters - Boston, MA, 1914-1917 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  1914, 1915, 1917
- Market Truckmen - New York, NY, 1927 (Box 16, Folder 60)
- Machinery Teamsters - South Chicago, IL, 1915 (Box 16, Folder 61)
- Machinery Teamsters - Chicago, IL, 1913-1923 (Box 16, Folder 62)
  1913, 1915, 1919, 1923
- Milk Wagon Drivers - Washington D.C., 1916 (Box 16, Folder 63)
- Milk Wagon Drivers - South Chicago, IL, 1915-1920 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  1915, 1916, 1919, 1920
- Milk Wagon Drivers - Chicago, IL, 1912-1924 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  1912, 1916-1921, 1924
- Milk Wagon Drivers - San Francisco, CA, 1912-1926 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  1912, 1916, 1917, 1920, 1923-1926
- Milk Wagon Drivers - Boston, MA, 1913-1922 (Box 16, Folder 67)
  1913, 1914, 1915, 1917-1920, 1922
- Milk Wagon Drivers - Minneapolis, MN, 1922 (Box 16, Folder 68)
- Milk Wagon Drivers - St. Paul, MN, 1919-1923 (Box 16, Folder 69)
- Milk Wagon Drivers - Cleveland, OH, 1916-1920 (Box 16, Folder 70)
- Milk Wagon Drivers - Rochester, NY, 1916-1922 (Box 16, Folder 71)
- Milk Wagon Drivers - Seattle, WA, 1915 (Box 16, Folder 72)
- Milk Wagon Drivers - Newark, NJ, 1919-1921 (Box 16, Folder 73)
- Milk Wagon Drivers - New York, NY, 1915-1925 (Box 16, Folder 74)
  1915, 1916, 1919, 1922, 1925
- Milk Wagon Drivers - St. Louis, MO, 1915-1924 (Box 16, Folder 75)
  1915, 1917, 1919, 1920, 1923, 1924
- Mineral Water Drivers - Newark, NJ, 1915-1917 (Box 16, Folder 76)
- Newspaper Delivery Drivers - Chicago, IL, 1916-1924 (Box 16, Folder 77)
- Newspaper Wagon Drivers - Boston, MA, 1914-1921 (Box 16, Folder 78)
  1914, 1918, 1921
- Oil Wagon Drivers - Cincinnati, OH, 1924 (Box 16, Folder 79)
- Packing House Teamsters - Chicago, IL, 1913-1924 (Box 16, Folder 80)
  1913, 1916, 1918, 1920-1924
- Piano Movers - St. Louis, MO, 1918-1926 (Box 16, Folder 81)
  1918, 1919, 1924, 1926
- Piano Movers - New York, NY, 1915-1923 (Box 16, Folder 82)
  1915, 1917, 1920, 1921, 1923
- Piano Moving Teamsters - Chicago, IL, 1911-1926 (Box 16, Folder 83)
  1911, 1916, 1917, 1921, 1926
- Produce Drivers - Philadelphia, PA, 1918 (Box 16, Folder 84)
- Retail Delivery Drivers - San Francisco, CA, 1914-1916 (Box 16, Folder 85)
  1914, 1915, 1916
- Retail Delivery Drivers - San Francisco, CA, 1913-1920 (Box 16, Folder 86)
- Roofing Teamsters - Chicago, IL, 1914-1927 (Box 16, Folder 87)
  1914, 1915, 1917, 1918, 1919, 1924, 1927
- Sanitary Wagon Drivers - Chicago, IL, 1914 (Box 16, Folder 88)
- Scrap Iron and Metal Teamsters - Chicago, IL, 1914 (Box 16, Folder 89)
- Soft Drink and Mineral Water Drivers - Cincinnati, OH, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 90)
- Soda and Mineral Water Wagon Drivers - Chicago, IL, 1911-1917 (Box 16, Folder 91)
  1911, 1916, 1917
- Stable and Garage Employees - San Francisco, CA, 1916 (Box 16, Folder 92)
- Stone, Lime and Cement Teamsters - Chicago, IL, 1912-1917 (Box 16, Folder 93)
  1912, 1913, 1914, 1916, 1917
- Street Railway Drivers - Chicago, IL, 1913-1920 (Box 16, Folder 94)
  1913, 1916, 1920
- Taxi Drivers - Boston, MA, 1914-1919 (Box 16, Folder 95)
  1914, 1916, 1918, 1919
- Taxicab Chauffeurs - Philadelphia, PA, 1915-1917 (Box 16, Folder 96)
- Tea and Coffee Drivers - Chicago, IL, 1913-1926 (Box 16, Folder 97)
  1913, 1916, 1919, 1926
- Tea and Coffee Salesmen - Detroit, MI, 1916 (Box 16, Folder 98)
- Tea and Coffee Drivers - St. Louis, MO, 1917 (Box 16, Folder 99)
- Team Drivers - Kansas City, MO, 1914-1918 (Box 16, Folder 100)
  1914, 1915, 1918
- Team Drivers - Duluth, MN, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 101)
- Theatrical Drivers - New York, NY, 1913-1926 (Box 16, Folder 102)
  1913, 1919, 1924, 1925, 1926
- Theatrical Drivers - Boston, MA, 1916-1917 (Box 16, Folder 103)
- Truck Drivers - Springfield, MA, 1915 (Box 16, Folder 104)
- Truck Drivers - Chicago, IL, 1912-1925 (Box 16, Folder 105)
  1912, 1915-1922, 1925
- Truck Teamsters - Boston, MA, 1913-1927 (Box 16, Folder 106)
  1913, 1917, 1918, 1924, 1925, 1927
- Truck Drivers - Cincinnati, OH, 1914-1921 (Box 16, Folder 107)
  1914, 1915, 1916, 1918, 1921
- Truck Drivers - New York, NY, 1927 (Box 16, Folder 108)
- Taxicab Drivers - Newark, NJ, 1920 (Box 16, Folder 109)
- Truck Drivers - Newark, NJ, 1915-1925 (Box 16, Folder 110)
  1915, 1916, 1917, 1918, 1925
- Truck Drivers - Delawanna, NJ, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 111)
- Truck Drivers - Cleveland, OH, 1915-1924 (Box 16, Folder 112)
  1915, 1918, 1921, 1923, 1924
- Truck Drivers - New York, NY, 1904-1925 (Box 16, Folder 113)
  1904, 1914-1919, 1922-1925
- Van Drivers - St. Louis, MO, 1915 (Box 16, Folder 114)
- Van Drivers - Cleveland, OH, 1915-1927 (Box 16, Folder 115)
  1915, 1918, 1921-1924, 1927
- Van Drivers - Cincinnati, OH, 1916-1922 (Box 16, Folder 116)
  1916, 1917, 1920, 1922
- Van Drivers - Chicago, IL, 1914-1923 (Box 16, Folder 117)
  1914,-1920, 1923
- Commercial Telegraphers - N/A, 1919 (Box 16, Folder 118)
- Commercial Telegraphers - Pittsburgh, PA, 1905 (Box 16, Folder 119)
- Commercial Telegraphers - El Paso, TX, 1905 (Box 16, Folder 120)
- Commercial Telegraphers - Chicago, IL, 1920-1923 (Box 16, Folder 121)
- Commercial Telegraphers - New York, NY, 1905 (Box 16, Folder 122)
- Commercial Telegraphers - Pacific Coast, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 123)
- Commercial Telegraphers - Canada, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 124)
- Commercial Telegraphers - Louisville, KY, 1904 (Box 16, Folder 125)
- Commercial Telegraphers - N/A, 1921-1924 (Box 16, Folder 126)
  1921, 1923, 1924
- Telephone Operators - Boston, MA, 1917-1923 (Box 16, Folder 127)
- Telephone Operators - Taylorville, IL, 1919 (Box 16, Folder 128)
- Telephone Operators - Coshocton, OH, 1920 (Box 16, Folder 129)
- Telephone Operators - Butte, MT, 1924 (Box 16, Folder 130)